<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 08:08:09 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Cloud]]></title><url><![CDATA[out-sourcing]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Cloud]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[5]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;h1&gt;
	&lt;span style=\&quot;font-family:quicksand;\&quot;&gt;Cloud Services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	&lt;img alt=\&quot;\&quot; src=\&quot;http://www.tobomedia.com/network_systems/data/uploads/cloud_graph.png\&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=\&quot;sidebar\&quot; class=\&quot;right\&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What&rsquo;s it like to work in the cloud?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
A lot like working on your desktop, only freer.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you need to access a Word document such as an urgent proposal while away from the office, you can.  From your phone, tablet, laptop or any other internet enabled device you can post your comments and edits , and save them.  Colleagues can then work on the document immediately.  It&rsquo;s a whole lot faster and more effective than emailing versions around.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you&rsquo;re with a customer and need to access information on your internal database you can, immediately.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
And if your tablet or phone is lost, stolen or breaks all you need to do is find another device to get back on the internet, then worry about replacing the one that&rsquo;s gone, not the data on it.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;content\&quot; &gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;
	Let us demist the cloud for you. Cloud computing has now matured; it&amp;rsquo;s reliable, secure, cost effective and has the potential to significantly reduce costs, and increase reliability in your business. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the best IT solutions in ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Actually, if you have a social network account with services like Facebook, Twitter or Linkedin you&amp;rsquo;re already using the cloud without knowing it. All the cloud really means is that your software and data sit remotely on a server in a third party network rather than on a drive in your PC or office based server. Your access is via a broadband connection, from pretty much any device or location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	You benefit in two key ways. Firstly is the obvious cost savings; your capex will reduce significantly. You won&amp;rsquo;t need a server or to cover the costs associated with it such as maintenance, storage space, risk and eventual replacement. The second is the anywhere, anytime access (see sidebar).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The transition can be smooth and seamless. We&amp;rsquo;re Microsoft Certified Partners, and Microsoft Certified Cloud Partners; our expertise will provide you with IT migration solutions into the cloud in a low-risk, low downtime, low-cost way that you&amp;rsquo;re comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	To find out how much cloud computing could save you get a FREE network audit worth &amp;pound;XXX and we can outline the costs you&amp;rsquo;ll save and the best starting points for a cloud migration.&amp;nbsp; Just click here or call us on&amp;nbsp; 0845 434 8610. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private></item>
