<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 10:54:01 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Support]]></title><url><![CDATA[support]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Support]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[3]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;h1&gt;
	&lt;span style=\&quot;font-family:quicksand;\&quot;&gt;IT Support for PC &amp;amp; Mac&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;img align=\&quot;right\&quot; alt=\&quot;\&quot; src=\&quot;http://www.tobomedia.com/network_systems/data/uploads/cloud_graph.png\&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;right\&quot; id=\&quot;sidebar\&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Disaster Recovery, because you have to consider the effects of a catastrophe.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Disaster recovery is essential risk mitigation.  What if a burst pipe from the office above leaks into the server room?  Just like buildings insurance, you don&rsquo;t want to fixate on it, but you have to have a plan in place against the kind of catastrophe which can destroy business critical data held on your machines.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The good news is that our Kaseya backup system is cost-effective, and with it&rsquo;s disk imaging approach, will enable a restoration onto completely blank hardware in under an hour.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
This will ensure your business can keep running smoothly, so all you&rsquo;ll need to worry about is clearing up, and not how you&rsquo;re going to run your business in the absence of everything you need to know about it.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;content\&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		IT Support is like insurance. As a business you want to know you&amp;rsquo;re protected but don&amp;rsquo;t want to pay more than you have to.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Other companies will brush aside cost pressures with a &amp;lsquo;but we&amp;rsquo;ve got the best IT solutions&amp;rsquo;; in these times it&amp;rsquo;s simply unrealistic. To offer you best value we&amp;rsquo;ve done two key things:&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		We&amp;rsquo;ve kept our overheads low, avoiding expensive sales, advertising and plush offices, and because we know you need reliability and quick problem solving we&amp;rsquo;ve developed a series of cost effective solutions to suit your needs.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;ul&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;
			&lt;strong&gt;Let us solve problems before they start.&lt;/strong&gt; Our Proactive managed service using leading edge software from Kaseya automatically checks and remediates recurring IT tasks like Patch Management, Audit and Inventory, Antivirus, Antimalware and a host of others. To keep costs managed we can configure the service to your needs.&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;
			&lt;strong&gt;Pay as you Go. &lt;/strong&gt; A more traditional service: your IT goes down, you call us and we fix it for you fast, either remotely while you watch or, if needs be, on site.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;/ul&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		We can combine elements of each of these services to tailor a package to suit your needs.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		To let you try us out risk free, we&amp;rsquo;re offering 2 hours of our awesome pay as you go service worth &amp;pound;XXX for free. Click here or call 0845 434 8610.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private></item>
