<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 08:13:09 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Telecoms]]></title><url><![CDATA[telecoms]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Telecoms]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[7]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;h1&gt;
	&lt;span style=\&quot;font-family:quicksand;\&quot;&gt;Telecoms/VOIP/Network Services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	&lt;img alt=\&quot;\&quot; src=\&quot;http://www.tobomedia.com/network_systems/data/uploads/outsourcing_graph.png\&quot; style=\&quot;width: 350px; height: 355px; \&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;right\&quot; id=\&quot;sidebar\&quot;&gt;
	&lt;h3&gt;
		Network Security, because an unprotected network leaves your business vulnerable to chaos.&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		The last person to leave your office every evening locks up and sets the alarm, right? With over 100,000 new web threats created daily you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to leave your network unsecured either.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Malware comes in many forms and for many purposes, but all are malign (hence the name). Often they are originated by foreign criminal gangs who want your information, or to hijack your domains. If they succeed it can cause chaos for you and a lasting lack of trust in your business.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Our network security solutions will cover all your bases such as: windows firewall, anti-virus, firewall router, and make it much much harder for any malign software prowling the web to break in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;content\&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Our VOIP solution won&amp;rsquo;t drop you, and it&amp;rsquo;s quality is as clear as any normal phone line. The only difference is the price.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Our VOIP service runs through a private network, not the internet. So while you benefit from cheaper calls you don&amp;rsquo;t suffer the quality problems that public internet based solutions have got a reputation for.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		VOIP is just one area of our network expertise. We can install and manage ADSL and SDSL; as well as all the cabling your network will need.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		If you like the sound of these solutions but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start, then we&amp;rsquo;ll give you a free network audit worth &amp;pound;XXX. You can work out how you can save money on telephony and across your network. Just click here or call 0845 434 8610.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private></item>
