<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 08:18:52 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Hardware]]></title><url><![CDATA[hardware]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[hardware]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[2]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;h1&gt;
	&lt;span style=\&quot;font-family:quicksand;\&quot;&gt;Hardware &amp;amp; Software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	&lt;img alt=\&quot;\&quot; src=\&quot;http://www.tobomedia.com/network_systems/data/uploads/it_sup_graph.png\&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;right\&quot; id=\&quot;sidebar\&quot;&gt;
	&lt;h3&gt;
		Mobile Working, because to be productive you may need to take the office with you.&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		If you or your employees spend time travelling, or need to respond to issues outside of business hours, or have a job role (like sales or field service) that&amp;rsquo;s primarily away from the office, then mobile working will greatly increase your productivity.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Mobile working is simply having access to your office based systems while away from them, with all the security, and speed you&amp;rsquo;d expect.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		We&amp;rsquo;re able to provide an array of cost effective solutions using a variety of different technologies to help balance your needs with your budget. We&amp;rsquo;ll even give you a free audit to recommend an implementation and plan so you can take your office with you when you go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=\&quot;content\&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Choosing Hardware and Software can feel overwhelming. There&amp;rsquo;s so much choice it&amp;rsquo;s tempting just to buy what you know in order to make a decision.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Trouble is you&amp;rsquo;ll probably end up paying more than you need for IT solutions that don&amp;rsquo;t really meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		At Network Systems we have both product and market knowledge, and access to the world&amp;rsquo;s best performing technologies from brands like: Microsoft, Cisco, Compaq, Dell, Toshiba, Novell and others.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		You can be sure that you&amp;rsquo;ll get optimal IT solutions for your current and emerging needs; we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this for years.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		If your network is creaking but you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to start fixing it then give us a call on 0845 434 8610, and we&amp;rsquo;ll perform a free Network Risk Audit worth &amp;pound;XXX for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private></item>
